if you're happy with your drawing until
you have to color the skin these tips
might help
first you want to select the base color
of the skin so this should just be kind
of the color you want it to be when it's
not in shade or in highlight
and once you have that selected you want
to take that mid color and put it to the
side
next you want to pick a color that is
both darker and redder than the mid tone
for a super pale character i like to use
something really red
i find that characters with darker
complexions can often go a little
farther into this pink zone and it can
still look nice which is trickier to do
with the lighter skin characters then
you pick your highlight
which can be lighter and cooler
place the darker color in key points
like under the eyes on the tips of the
ears around the nose
then gently start to blend it in
then carefully add a couple little
highlights
and blend
you can add details like scars or
freckles and you're done